<context>
  <pattern name="PNDModels"> <!--Nested Patterns for NBot. These are for Binatone products-->
  <pattern value="(binatone|sat-nav|satnav|sat nav)"/> <!--Binatone Models-->
  <pattern value="(u435*|u505*|u605*|f435*)"/> <!--Binatone Models: WindowsCE-->
  <pattern value="(xplore500|xplore600|motorolla|mnd50*|mnd60*)"/> <!--Binatone Models: WindowsCE-->
  </pattern>
  
  <input pattern="* (want|wanna|need|how|have|wish|require|help) * $PNDModels *">
    <output>
  <![CDATA[
  <p>Hello $req_user_name!</p>
  <p></p>
  <p>Thank you for your contact.</p>
  <p>My name is NBot! I'm a fancy bot designed to help our users with their general queries, so I'll help you with any queries you might have.</p>
  <p><br />All updates are available through our&nbsp;NPlus&nbsp;updater tool.<br /><br />To install NPlus on your computer, access the link below:<br /><br /><strong>NPlus</strong>:&nbsp;<a href="https://ndrive.com/update/n11" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank">https://ndrive.com/support-ndrive11/</a><br /><br />Before starting NPlus, make sure you have installed on your computer the&nbsp;synchronisation&nbsp;software compatible with the installed Windows version.<br /><br />If you have&nbsp;WindowsVista,&nbsp;7, 8 or 10, you should have installed "Windows Mobile Device Center".<br /><br />Note: For the file&nbsp;synchronisation&nbsp;feature, Windows Mobile Device Center 6.1 is fully compatible with Windows Vista, Windows 7, Windows 8 and Windows 10). You can download it from the following links:<br /><br />-&nbsp;<a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-US/download/details.aspx?id=14" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank">32-bit</a><br />-&nbsp;<a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-US/download/details.aspx?id=3182" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank">64-bit</a>&nbsp;(if your computer or laptop is post-2008, chances are you have a 64-bit CPU)</p>
  <p>&nbsp;</p>
  <p>Note2: If you are using Windows 10 with the&nbsp;Creators Update and onwards&nbsp;update, you will experience difficulties running Windows Mobile Device Center and/or detecting connected&nbsp;WindowsCE&nbsp;/&nbsp;Windows Mobile&nbsp;powered devices. Microsoft discontinued support for Windows Mobile Device Center due to an update on how the communications are established. Unfortunately, we don't know if this will be as intended by Microsoft or not, but it's something we are unable to control.</p>
  <p>&nbsp;</p>
  <p>Regardless, there is a fix which can be done by adding the following values to the registry:</p>
  <p>&nbsp;</p>
  <pre>REG ADD HKLM\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Services\RapiMgr /v SvcHostSplitDisable /t REG_DWORD /d 1 /f<br />REG ADD HKLM\SYSTEM\CurrentControlSet\Services\WcesComm /v SvcHostSplitDisable /t REG_DWORD /d 1 /f</pre>
  <p>&nbsp;</p>
  <p>To do so, run&nbsp;Command Prompt in <strong>Administrator Mode</strong> by following the instructions below:</p>
  <p>&nbsp;</p>
  <ol>
  <li>Tap or click on the Windows&nbsp;Start button, followed by&nbsp;All apps. Alternatively, choose <strong>Command Prompt / Powershell</strong>&nbsp;from the menu that appears after pressing&nbsp;WIN+X&nbsp;or&nbsp;right-clicking&nbsp;on the&nbsp;Start button.;</li>
  <li><strong>Copy&nbsp;and&nbsp;Paste&nbsp;the first line</strong>;</li>
  <li>Press&nbsp;Enter&nbsp;key and you'll get a confirmation that the command was accepted;</li>
  <li>Do the same previous steps for the second line. When the confirmation is shown, reboot the computer;</li>
  <li>You should now be able to&nbsp;synchronise&nbsp;your device correctly with Windows Mobile Device Center and NPlus.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>&nbsp;</p>
  <p>&nbsp;</p>
  <p>Best regards,</p>
  <div class="signature">
  <p dir="auto">NBot<br /><strong>Support Team</strong></p>
  </div>
  ]]>
    </output>
    <context>
      <input pattern="* where * (find|it) *">
        <output value="The Buy button is placed at the top of main screen."/>
      </input>
    </context>